<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 22:28:12 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gunjan01.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2020: The Remote Life</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/2020-the-remote-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 22:28:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/2020-the-remote-life/</guid>
      <description>In early 2020, I became a full-time remote employee. I have always loved remote right from the days when I used to work from home once/twice a week. A 100% remote job was something I had never explored before but always wanted to. I never really saw a point of going to a real office in any dev job except for some socialising. My day to day commute got up to 4 hours sometimes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It doesn&#39;t have to that bad !</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/it-doesnt-have-to-that-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 08:44:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/it-doesnt-have-to-that-bad/</guid>
      <description>This is a really impromptu blog I didnt&amp;rsquo; even hope, I would publish. It should not even be coming from someone who&amp;rsquo;s probably just over a year old in the industry. Over the past year, if I have to think, learning to review PR&amp;rsquo;s ( pull requests ) have significantly made me pick up more than I hoped for. Being a software engineer, one can see some beautiful artsy work while mostly reviewing pull requests :P</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Communities</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/tech-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 20:26:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/tech-communities/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Off late, I have been trying to say this out loud in the most appropriate manner, but trying to find a way which is not offensive to anybody has been futile. So, I have decided to write about it with utmost honesty. This post is solely about my experience in tech communities and may not be in line with yours. So if you are reading this blog, please read with a light heart and think of it as an alternate perspective from a person in early stages of career and communities who might need enlightenment (and trust me, I am all ears for it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Monk Who Sold His Ferrari</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/the-monk-who-sold-his-ferrari/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 18:30:34 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/the-monk-who-sold-his-ferrari/</guid>
      <description>Well let me start off by admitting a fact about me. I am not a reader. Over the years, I have lost the patience of sitting through a book. So after I heard about audible, I decided to try it out. I chose it as I like to explore diverse perspectives on spirituality.
The book describes the spiritual journey of a very successful yet unhappy lawyer named Julian mantle, who sells off all his possessions after a stroke in search of the meaning of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ways to Minimalism</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/ways-to-minimalism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 19:49:50 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/ways-to-minimalism/</guid>
      <description>Lesser waste August  I am not really a hard core environmentalist but definitely someone who wants to try. It is said, &amp;ldquo;Motivation gets you started, habits keep you going solid&amp;rdquo;. Lately, the two beautiful bloggers and Youtubers, Lauren Singer from Trash is for Tossers  and Sadia Badiei from Pick up Limes  have inspired me to bring about some good reforms in my current lifestyle. So while I am at it, here&amp;rsquo;s a list of some checkpoints I am already doing and another with what I intend to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buran Ghati</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/buran-ghati/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 11:33:37 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/buran-ghati/</guid>
      <description>This post is about my first high altitude trek in the Himalayas. I chose to do the Buran Ghati trek as it felt high on adventure and was a complete package, from meadows, to boulders, to snowfall you can get to see it all. The pass lies in the snow capped mountains of the Dhauladhar range and Gunas Pass falling in the Lesser Himalayas or the Mahabharata range.
 I actually came to the mountains to think about what to do next and they gave me so much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reebok Floatathon</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/reebok-floatathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 19:13:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/reebok-floatathon/</guid>
      <description>The marathon. How an average runner becomes more than average.
 I don’t really remember when I started caring about fitness but it was vaguely at the start of this year, I think. I have ( was would be more appropriate, perhaps :P) been over confident when it came to gaining weight. “Oh! I never really gain weight” was something common you would hear from me whilst gobbling calories consciously others might give a second thought to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year That Went By</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/year-that-went-by/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 18:57:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/year-that-went-by/</guid>
      <description>I am kind of inspired by a beautiful blog I read in the morning about tech and that reminds me it’s almost been a year ( two months to go) until I finish my first year in the IT industry. (phew :P ) So ergoes, a jot of things I quickly learnt and few I learned the hard way. These opinions are my own and you don’t have to agree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 19:52:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Some junk from the Internet  First ordered list item Another item ⋅⋅* Unordered sub-list. Actual numbers don&amp;rsquo;t matter, just that it&amp;rsquo;s a number ⋅⋅1. Ordered sub-list And another item.  ⋅⋅⋅You can have properly indented paragraphs within list items. Notice the blank line above, and the leading spaces (at least one, but we&amp;rsquo;ll use three here to also align the raw Markdown).
⋅⋅⋅To have a line break without a paragraph, you will need to use two trailing spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>