<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech on </title>
    <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/categories/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tech on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 08:44:55 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gunjan01.github.io/categories/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It doesn&#39;t have to that bad !</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/it-doesnt-have-to-that-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 08:44:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/it-doesnt-have-to-that-bad/</guid>
      <description>This is a really impromptu blog I didnt&amp;rsquo; even hope, I would publish. It should not even be coming from someone who&amp;rsquo;s probably just over a year old in the industry. Over the past year, if I have to think, learning to review PR&amp;rsquo;s ( pull requests ) have significantly made me pick up more than I hoped for. Being a software engineer, one can see some beautiful artsy work while mostly reviewing pull requests :P</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Communities</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/tech-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 20:26:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/tech-communities/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Off late, I have been trying to say this out loud in the most appropriate manner, but trying to find a way which is not offensive to anybody has been futile. So, I have decided to write about it with utmost honesty. This post is solely about my experience in tech communities and may not be in line with yours. So if you are reading this blog, please read with a light heart and think of it as an alternate perspective from a person in early stages of career and communities who might need enlightenment (and trust me, I am all ears for it).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year That Went By</title>
      <link>https://gunjan01.github.io/year-that-went-by/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 18:57:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunjan01.github.io/year-that-went-by/</guid>
      <description>I am kind of inspired by a beautiful blog I read in the morning about tech and that reminds me it’s almost been a year ( two months to go) until I finish my first year in the IT industry. (phew :P ) So ergoes, a jot of things I quickly learnt and few I learned the hard way. These opinions are my own and you don’t have to agree.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>